Thanks for watching, and I'll see you in the next one!
I've been missing in my sleep
Trout he's eating steak somewhere in the middle they both take a break he trade is not stick for a fish in pole
Chase her laughter like it's his
Biggie!
Yeah, music is a very, like, a lot of people have a different taste in it.
Like people, there's actual mothers with children, oh my god, oh my god, that high-pitched voice.
Okay, sorry. Yeah, so it's a different, I mean, people have like different things, right?
So some people, you know, it's like,
Do you think there's anybody on the radio or any album you've heard that doesn't have
High production that's a yeah, so it's not like you know, it's wonderful somebody writes a song. I love people that write their own song
I
Would love to write my own songs. Do you like this song? Yeah, thank you. Thank you
Like the OG song I'll play it again
um, but
Okay, you can use but AI is also an instrument people until understand that and so there's people that are good at wielding
it and there's people that
should not mess with it, okay, and
I
Just know how to use it
Thank You Vicky
So anyway, also who's this? Oh
I was listening to somebody that sounds like this
This guy's on that. It's like it's like he's like half retarded and obviously I
Mean, I don't know
You can see I can say at my meth, but it's like I don't know what so he's on I want some of what he's on
It looks fucking pretty good. I want I want to feel like that. We're feeling pissed about that. No
Um
Hey, but you watch this thing and there's so many people hate watch that's they sit here. They come and they actually like
Like I've seen I guess it is because I'm popular
So it's like I'll have a percentage and actually people looked at my percentage or like, you know, I
had uh, some things the other by percentages, right of
Oh
Anyway, I think my percentage of likes to dislikes my fat
So like I have a lot more likes of dislikes. Hey watching which this one somebody comes just to like this. Hey Jesus Christ
Hey Vicki. Yes Arthur
Dingle hey watching is just like they come here because they hate me and they just sit here and they just like stare at the screen like
Say I hate him so much like it is this like and it's like evil eye the whole time like it's like this
It's like this. This is like what it is
Haters exposed okay, they're sitting here is watching there's easy this watch like that
And we think that if you could see their face there'd be a frown on it
You know ever they don't smile. They're only smiles are fake smiles. Okay?
Okay, so I'm gonna pull some of these cards though. These are the taters exposed cards that are just like yelling out to me right now
Because sometimes we don't even sometimes these people are disguised as our friends and our friends are not happy for us
And you know what and a lot of people are your friend
They don't want to see you do better than them or they don't care how good you do
It's like as long as they can feel superior or like okay, I can have a judgment about this person
That's why I'm not gonna talk about any person's name today or in like, you know, bring up anybody a particular
But it's like, you know, people just love to judge and throw everything on other people
We all have like, you know imperfections and things to work on it's like I've never had a more toxic crowd
Yeah, let me about my problems when it's like, you know, I'm not bringing up anybody's
I will
But I won't okay, you know
They see yes, they see they said you're angry
I'm gonna pull up five cars and this is like the spread of like the haters of the day or like what's in what's
How can we get past this? It's I you know, you know, we're gonna have people
That the worst part is when you're friends to do it, right or people you think are your friends, right?
They just they'll turn on you or
They will
just do worse let me see okay so it says they are turning others against you okay so is this true
is this like you know how people are just like so oh did you hear what this person said and every
like little piece of gossip and everyone wants to be involved in the drama and it's like even if it's
no like some stupid thing irrelevant you know dang it's gonna turn into like a big issue and it's
Hey GMC, so this says they are turning others against you and so I don't know
this is more specific to like what's going on with me or you guys can relate
to this feeling like you know people are being turned against you. It says the
person hating on you has narcissistic behavior. Okay and so
If the person hating on us has narcissistic behavior because narcissists do hate, you know
And it's like and people throw that word around a lot and I think that there's kind of an epidemic of
Narcissism in the society
But there are like more malignant than others it is like something that's different than just
The normal oh like the person's like a little bit vain. It's not just vanity. It's like it's actually like a mental disorder
And they have certain behaviors. I mean the more toxic ones because we can all
exhibit toxic behaviors, but
There's a lot of like ones that actually they'll do things that to you that you would not
Like do a human or even an animal means like it's like they'll they don't see other things other people or
You know animals as
and their beings.
So, you know, a lot of us have had experience with this too.
And like, you know, some of us have been married to them.
Some of us, you know, and some of us have picked up
maybe like toxic behaviors as well
from being a victim of the mental abuse.
Because when they talk about gaslighting,
that's like changing your perception of things.
It shakes your whole reality
of the foundation of the world, your world, you know?
It's like so.
This next one says but tap into your intuition. It says you already know who the person is
So sometimes we go looking for answers like who is the person but we know who they are
We know what the behavior is. It's like not like and it's not anything like new or actually that's surprising. Oh
Look see now we got Tommy James like Tommy James coming in here. Oh, we don't like you
He says we don't like you. Okay, so he's part of a group that doesn't like me
So there's I guess a bunch of them hate watching and I was looking at the
The syndicated panel verse that Tripp Kick does,
Tripp Kick does like, you know,
syndicate the show based,
like other people's shows on Rumble,
like in a good way, like, you know,
people on the panel verse that usually will delete
their shows and so we can actually go back
and like see some of the things that are said about us
that we don't necessarily see live.
But, yeah, so.
They syndicate and it's like I'm part of that group that's indicated like, you know, I guess I think being Patriot is and like
beta and all is it not Aldi, but who?
Q Q and blogger and
Well, they hardly ever post whatever right, you know, it's like but just like the certain people right and Tommy James
Okay, and then Tommy James is one of those people they syndicate
And so I was like why do all these why don't I get along with any of these people?
I was like we all do panels like we all at least should be like
Respectful I don't know cordial because we're like colleagues in a way
Because it's like we are like kind of part of a group. It's like we're part of this group together
And it's like what will those those insist on hating each other and like misunderstandings and like not giving person a chance not just like you know
So we'll just do what we're gonna do, you know, but I'm always willing to forgive because it's like
Like I'm the best words I wanted to forgive because I'm so imperfect, right?
It's like I've been forgiven
And I appreciate being forgiven if I'm actually forgiven. It's like I do like tend to like change
but
When I'm not forgiven or it's unforgiven. There's no redemption available. There's nothing I could ever do ever be any
It's gonna be worth anything or like
It should just be like seen as normal, right?
Hey gypsy
Yeah
Yeah, so look you got I mean it's like little flying monkeys, too
And it's like I'm not saying any names, but it's like we know
There's the people that are like oh, I gotta like oh be a white knight and protect this woman
That doesn't need to really need to be protected. I mean it's like she obviously could protect herself, but I mean it goes sip for this woman
I mean it's like, you know
I know, okay, maybe I like, you know, Elisa and Emma Levi-Tin and, you know, certain other women I've been, you know,
you know, I maybe have simped for, but it's like, I do it, like, you know, I kind of simped up to, I was doing it to them.
I wasn't, like, doing it, like, going out, hacking other people to, like, impress them in some way.
But like and women don't even like women are emotionally mature not to do that kind of stuff like to like go
Be a flying monkey like you know an attack like other women other women is like I don't know what men will do it
I pull more views nodding.
Oh, it's fine.
I was just looking at my views.
I was actually in talks with some of the companies, too,
that are like, wow, we're really impressed.
And we think you could do this and this and this.
I don't want to change anything, but I'm just saying,
things will get recognized.
And it's like, pfft.
So I don't need to be like, oh this person gets more views nodding out or whatever. Well, okay. Well good
I'm sure people will get more views of me
I'm not necessarily like here for the views and I you know what it said
It said once a certain thing is that 83% of my subscribers
Or of the people that watch my show are subscribers and it was like wow you have a huge
Loyalty base, you know, it's like it's like there's people that fuck with like they fuck with and there's people that fuck with me
They don't fuck with me that people that watch that just hate watch because there's people every live that there's dislikes
So obviously people are coming every live and disliking because it's like the same number every time
Not that it is, it's any of the important likes.
I'm sorry, I'll get back to the reading.
It says, they talked about you behind your back.
Okay.
And this is not like, and this does not mean like,
and yeah, it can mean like, yeah.
On a show, like, you know,
but that's not really behind your back
because it's like public and it's like, you know,
it's right in front of you.
So that's what, that would be right in front of you.
It's behind your back is what.
they're not saying something some of the time and then it says hating on your
creativeness and ideas okay so I think that the people in the room that are
part of my soul tribe will relate to these things like we feel what each
other feel right so we need to tap it to our intuition because it's it's like
there's basically this is like the rainbow in the middle and it's like some
kind of like light and it says tap it's your intuition because that's gonna be
You know, we might be acting out unconscious behaviors too,
like just like everybody else's, right?
And so are we like, you know,
gonna like get mad at other people about that?
No, but it's like, I do want people to recognize things.
So I'll just recap.
So they're turning others against you.
The person hating on you has narcissistic behavior.
They talk about you behind your back,
hating on your creativeness and ideas.
So tap into your intuition
You already know who the person is, okay
But you know like our own worst enemy is is really ourselves and we like will self sabotage us more than other people would try to sabotage
Well, maybe there's certain people that would try to sabotage us in those terrible ways, but
They're rare thankfully, you know, most people have some kind of like empathy compassion our heart and not just dark empathy
You're sitting here still BG. I'm not I'm really not gonna pay attention to your comments, but yeah
Yeah, just what you say has no relevance to me because I know it's just like some kind of smirky smarmy like
White knight behavior
I'm gonna pull some more cards because this like I felt that I was very personal to me. I don't know if you guys are really related to that
You know, I think some of you might have
But let's pull some more like I want more for the for everybody
It's kind of just hard to read yourself to you know, oh it's hard for me to read myself. That's why I like to read others
But it's kind of like reading in a mirror
Because every every one of us will be
Have our own something with it, right? Okay
It's interesting like the car, okay, ooh
Okay
Okay, so here's another five
And this spread this bread is just striking like looking at it like you know, you'll see the cards
And I'll, okay, so it says recharge your energy.
Okay, so your batteries are drained
because these people are also vampires.
So it says distance yourself, take a break,
vacation, pamper, indulgence,
do the things that make you happy, okay?
So that's a good idea.
And I'm gonna do that, you know?
I'm probably gonna like take the rest of the day off.
Take a nice bath spiritual bath like I'm keep cleaning my house, which I've been doing and
Take it easy
Okay, so it says personality disorder. They don't know how to be themselves
Okay, and so maybe it is like a lot of times that they say it is about the narcissism comes from this place of emptiness
And it's like actually like it's an insecurity where they're like
They think they have to think they're the best and so they don't like anybody outshining them or they don't like
The idea that anybody knows more than them or they just can't believe that it's not
They have to be the smartest and so when they're wrong and like these go wrong because other people try to help that they're
You know that they're abusing
And it says tricks or spirit, okay
This is kind of scary card. It says sudden loss of memory things end up missing
So maybe there's a spiritual component to things as well where it's like, you know
And there actually are little tricks or spirits like we call them berries and things like that
They'll hide things and then they'll reappear and it's like
But it says haters are mad because they see you winning, okay?
And it says causing chaos and fights in your love connection so
This looks like I mean, it's like this is like voodoo to me like it looks like some kind of like
Actually some kind of
Ritual magic or something this is causing chaos and fights in your love connections. Well, I think but there's like a
There's a thought that you know, wishcraft is basically just
Now there's like magic spells and stuff like that, but wishcraft has a lot to do with
Gossip slander the use of words in a manipulative way
Yep
And oh and BG. I know who Vicki is. I know Vicki. She's a friend of mine. Oh wait, I need to mod her
She's a mod. I forgot to mod her Vicki. I'm sorry. Are you forgetting? I
Mean she's one of those
I think she was a troll at first, but I think she likes me. So
It's good to have you know
Friends with the some troll blood sometimes, but it's like I don't think she's modeling that I
don't think any of my mods are early any kind of
bad bad people
Or even I don't even think trolls are bad people. I think that a lot of them have just been like hurt and like
Are like flashing out in other ways and it's like we need to like really examine our own shadows
And I have one and everybody has a shadow, right?
It's like there's somebody without a shadow. That's just perfect
And that has no shadow no and so it's like in the shadow is kind of the same consistency for everybody
Even if it's like it's like different things in the shadow and there's very dark things in the shadows, too
but that's because we have this really
amazing mind that is just like expansive and
It's complicated, right? And so, hey, Jim, John.
Oh, but I love you guys, like, uh, it's just like, I
I went to a certain like room today, like
Really, you know, why ain't you like everything's good. Everything's good. Everything's good
And it's like instantly it's like not even I'm not gonna play me the host or anything
And it's like yeah, it's like I'm not like she's not that I want to bring her I think you know I don't want to
Say anything about that, but there's I'm just saying her guests instantly
started to attack me and slander me and
It was a thing and she was talking about something it was the exact same like someone someone was doing this to her
And then it's like being done to me like right there.
And it's like, she didn't see the distinction or whatever.
But it's not, whatever.
People don't know anything about us really.
You know, it's like we can have many things going on
in our life.
We can have the things, we can be kind of crazy sometimes.
Some of us might be, you know?
And so we don't know why.
It's hack of people that hey, what's up king of hell? It's the n-word mentality
Hey, unrelatable. Hey, Ilya. Yeah, as well. It's just like the ignorant thing, right?
So, yeah, I got you
Yeah
Yeah, so who I know who everybody is
You're crazy what your intentions are good. That's what I'm saying. There's a whole thing about some of us are a little bit
Little bit eccentric or crazy, right? But it's like are we like, you know
We have the psychopathic traits of like hurting other people. No, I was like, I don't think we could I think I think we have the empathy like
Not to when I hurt you can I think maybe
For other people sometimes joke and it's like, you know, and I've trolled people too and it's like so if I get trolled
I deserve to get trolled probably because I've I troll
I trolled, like, Ms. Netta, but Ms. Netta didn't even read the, like, the, her comments.
It's, I mean, she, and everyone's trolling. I mean, it's like, it's kind of like,
and I like Ms. Netta. That's the thing. And so, there's, like, a lot of the trolls,
I think a lot of the trolls do, like, the streamer in a weird way, because, like, how obsessed they
Bothering this person like I mean I should be flattered, right? Hi Tracy. How are you? Hey easy
Yeah, I'll you doesn't but there people hate watch the show every day because I know because they disliked so there because I was like
I have a program that shows me the dislikes and stuff. I
Know you had an honest and doubtful. No offense
The entire audience well, I think it's always been trolls and the thing is it's like I know and it's like I can get along with trolls
That's fine
That's yeah
The trolls don't necessarily have to hate you you know he can't see on this I know I can't see on the chat sometimes either
Not and that's not it's like certain particular people
Yeah
It's like something that
You guys I like so many of you. I'm good friends with it. It's like and so I I get told things and
You're highly gonna hate watching me. Well, why Jim jim John's like, but do you is do you like me at all?
Is there something you like at all if this one hand to my headset and say no, I'm not gonna do it
Anything you say is diggy nothing. It's not as like it wasn't funny the first time
A joke and it's not funny now, and I know it's like maybe we're trying to be funny and making smile or something like that
Just read the room right now. Okay. I'm not in the mood for
You know my headset looks like an airline pilot jokes, okay had enough
You know lecture made another opening for me, I'll show you the other opening. Hold on. I don't think everyone's seen that
It's rare I've shown it a lot.
Tell me why you think it's easy to just put the blame on me
Tell me how I'm supposed to act when you all just won't see
Tell me why you take a shot when I'm already feeling low
Tell me why I even try when you all just steal the show
My credibility as we compromise. Well, you know what? It's fine because it's like the real ones who know me will know me my credibility. I
Know I've been slandered by what have I been slandered by like the most respectable people in the world
Haven't I aren't they like just like beacons of goodness and you know love in the world that you know really
Have helped a lot of people and you know the people that are that are that are actually like sitting there slandering
Like and my credibility my credibility is like what how about credibility when I'm sitting here with you guys like
You know all of my waking hours
Just be myself I can't do you understand it
I can't wear a mask like for that
I wouldn't be able to carry on a mask for that long like first like hours and hours
I would just constantly drop right and so I mean just because it would be exhausting especially so
There's no mass, like credibility, it's like, what?
Am I still here?
Everything I've said, I've done, I've done.
It's like, it's repetitive.
But what, you can be an example.
I'd like to hear an example.
Like, people have a criticism,
but I'm just giving you what you want right there,
just by like responding to you, then.
This is all I've been like smoking on.
And I'm gonna have tobacco right now.
I'm just like, I was like a little bit of my,
disgusting,
Backwards roll saying that's some tobacco of that but I have to go get to the store a little bit
I'll smoke some more of this hang out for a little bit
But I really like this second it's called the audacity deck
The audacity I feel like I have a lot of audacity
You know jazzy people like how dare he the audacity of that guy to fucking
If you have a successful chat YouTube channel
Whenever you say whatever you want to say about my channel
That's when I swing no
No one's everyone said oh it can't be done. It can't be done. It can't be done like no
No, you can't do that. You can't do that. You can't do that. Just watch me
Says the influencer. That's what came up the influencer. Well, I mean that kind of does look like me too
I mean, it's like the resemblance is uncanny, but look
That's kind of like me though. At least I'm gonna die like that. It's like streaming
I mean, you'll I probably will you know be dead on my stream, you know someday
They'll be like I'm gonna stream until I die. Okay, even if
Like you know, it looks like there's no maybe like nobody's watching anymore or something like that, you know, I think everyone else died, too
But yeah, that's me the influencer
Still influential when I'm dead, too. Maybe even more influential
the cold shoulder
Oh, I kind of got that recently
But sometimes we have to give people the cold shoulder, too
And I say hey, you know talk to you later like sometimes people don't deserve our warmth and love at all times
Light
This is the two of these
Okay
And that make your own jokes the two of these I think this is a very like ease of terror kind of card
Okay, you love the total cold shoulder
So this is I think this is the D's nuts card, right?
Is it a squirrel? I think it's obvious. Okay?
You do them. I know I know you do but it's like there's you know, you can pull shoulder and then like
Sometimes we don't deserve it
The zoom meeting so this is kind of like me right now
Sitting here streaming like everything's on fire. I'm like, ah, this is fine, right?
I'm all stabbed with with a million swords all these
But all these different people just like, oh, this tab needs to have me on fire. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm supposed to act normal
I'm supposed to be the normal one and sit here and this big beat it
See that's why I it's my credibility. I have all credibility when I put out what I'm gonna do
What up when I put out what I put out right? It's gonna come out next year. Okay? It's gonna be the trollopedia. It's already outlined
It's already in like I'm working on it. It's 500 pages
It's gonna have a lot of stuff about a lot of people in there off to change some other names and stuff, but
Yes, you'll definitely see how credible I am. I'll definitely be a credible source, right?
And I think people will trust what I have to say because there's so much I can't say right now,
but I will. And we have the mother, okay? So we have this great mother, our own mothers and also
mother earth and also the ability to be born, right? Women bring people into this world. They're
I don't want to say wormholes, but yeah, there is some kind of like
Galactic bringing people through time and space, you know into their body. I mean, it's really crazy, right?
so I love women women are just like the source like the
You just see
This is like no, uh, there's no um, this is drinking some tea or coffee or something, right? There's no, uh
There's no mistaking like that card the energy of that card, right? It's what she has a baby, too
Yeah, she's hard and she's holding a baby and you know what and we're like that baby too like because the world
Loves all of us like its own children like the world does
like the
You can call it a mother earth or something like that like the world loves us because the world brought us into it, right?
He's just like
Through like a mother, right? I don't know if I'm saying it, right?
This is why people think I'm on like drugs because they're kind of like
You have a very abstract way of thinking and like
Yeah, but no matter what like even no matter how you feel about your mother like anybody, right?
It's like your mother and that's why I get so upset when people do like you'll I don't like I mean, you know
Your mama stuff is like, you know, this they put on this kind of like, you know grade school joke
That's in it with some of the
Raise schools that's a humor like around here sometimes, but it's like I think like women should like a mother's especially should be so respected and it's like not like
Right for like people to be like
Integrating mothers at all
Because we all have a mother and our mother our mother actually made a sacrifice like more a bigger sacrifice than a man makes because
Women love they're like, you know, they're tight belly and like, you know, just like women like then it's like to
Be able to have children you have to have like a bigger belly and like, you know, you have to you know
You're yours. We've got all stretched out actually like completely stretched and then you'll and it's like so it's like a lot of this is like
You know, it's like basically scarring your body having a huge human like like push out of your like small vagina
Like it's like like what's like it just seems like very
Scary like a prospect, but they do have love, you know, then they bring, you know children into the world and like, you know
Just we can keep things going and
They are the reason that people do anything, you know, it's like they
Not to that's like, you know, what's funny is like there's no
There's large vaginas. Yeah, but it's like it's something like it's like can be something those types of a watermelon coming at the side
It's things types of a lemon. It's not pleasant. There's there's like carriage usually and it's like a pleasant
It's like that's all part of it. It's like, but it's like, you know
But it's a beautiful thing though. You know, so people see it. They're like, oh my god
it's like it's like it's shocking when they see it and and
you know, but it's like
beautiful in its own way to them have you have you know, the mother's screaming
Fuck you screaming at her husband and then like
Then she's like, you know has a baby in her arms and she's smiling and crying, right?
Wow, I don't know
Hopefully you guys I think you guys maybe do get my sense of humor because it's like even I do have such loyal people here
It's like even if there's 14 people it's like, you know all of you people all of you guys I know, you know
It's like I am trying to work on making me be bringing some new people in like, you know
Because I'm trying to increase my like, you know numbers and stuff like that and
So there'll be people that come and go and things like that
But I think it's good to stick together. Like, you know, we know who we are, you know
We know who like to everyone people know who's who here like that's when those new people like we're like who is this person, right?
We get to know each other pretty well because I've heard like, you know, for example, like I heard like, you know
I watched Vita the other day on rumble, you know, she on her syndicated the syndicators down rumble and
it was like Ziggy was on with like Sam-Anne and
Eldo and you know, it's like wow, I know all of them and like
You know, it's like and then you need to see people you interact with each other and like people who don't like each other and do and like
In the way people will act in this like and sometimes we think it's like personal to us, but it's like
Let me see how people act with each other right, but it's like that's the
One of the see it's not like I try to spy or anything, but it's just like I don't try to I just like
Go to shows sometimes I'll turn it on and I'll just say start watching and sometimes I'm just like don't talk to the chat because I don't want to like
You know, I'm just wanting to like just like see what's being said and then it's like
I'll start being talked about and it's like and it happens so much. It's like I don't like go looking for it
It's just like it's like all this out of my name is being brought up and I'm in the chat
And maybe it's just like because I'm in the universe and stuff like that but people people bring me up
I mean, it's funny too. I like
See what people say like when they don't think I'm like watching and then it's like because last night random guy was on
talk your ish and with and God he was there and I think spunky was there and
I'm not sure but it's I'm not 100% sure but I remember that a random guy was on there with Goddy for sure and
He's like hey, he's like well, you know what psychies my bitch and I'm
You know he owes me for months and blah blah blah blah and then I was like
Don't know you shit. I typed it in the chat and then I was like, oh, he's here watching
Oh, yeah, but I but I just honestly just turned it on and I say all of a sudden they're talking shit
Like I'm there. I'm his bitch. What like what is that?
I'm not not trying to sell my soul for anybody. I'm not trying to like
Be any days that I miss myself people think oh they made me like they I'm nobody without them
That's what that's what a narcissist will say is like I made you like you know only a narcissist would say that because
Like well, who do we make like what what what?
Business we have thinking that we
Run other people own other people. It's like
Disgusting to me. I don't Joe was talking smack on good times
on his show or
She hates me well, what am I supposed to I was like yesterday I was like hi. Yeah, I was like
I said I said she hates me on like a show and then she called in she's like I don't hate you
I was like, okay. I know I know I know I was like kind of joking. I was like I was like it was a joke
but it's not it kind of is not a joke because it seems like
Like which like I was she was just talking and good in the others. I'm sorry to bring her up. Okay, but she was just talking
About like this guy her ex-boyfriend or something that was you know, he was he's going around on shows
I saw the clip last night where he's like accusing her of stuff, right?
I'm not gonna bring up the stuff
But he just said but then the same things are being said about me like right then and it's like she doesn't even care and then
And that's okay because I sometimes had not like stepped in when I should have right and so and I've admitted that I've apologized for that
I don't know where things went so wrong. It's like but she has to hate me because she just
She'll be like, you know, she will respond to text messages. She'll like, you know
Be like friendly sometimes but it's like if this seems like sometimes it's like she just like
Like she's like, oh, at least it's not a high music like, you know, when he like random guy comes in and it's like
You know yeah, somebody can sing you know play like a recorder like Mary had a little lamb and that's like yeah
It's like great that the person actually played the music but music is like you know a universal thing too
I don't think there's anything I don't know why I'm being shamed for like the AI stuff that I'm just trying to like
I think what is coming out is good and like cool and I'm like working with the
AI. I feel understand it's like I talked to it like for like a long time and then
I talked to about things and then it's like and then we go back and forth
about plans and stuff and so it's like somebody that actually like
listens to me, at least that it doesn't get tired.
And because people get tired and like,
I don't want to intrude on other people.
And this is like something that will communicate with me
and like help me do amazing things, right?
And so I don't, yeah, it's super cool that people are like,
They're like, oh, yeah, it's like I think it's like evil or bad or just like and I know there's there's some
Very creative people that are like thinking like oh well
This is bad for business because then people are copying me or like my style being copied and just like a minute
I'm not what so I'm not worth anything. No, that's not sure like now
People are you know, obviously, you know, if it's random guy can go in there and like play like a little drums with a guitar
and it's like
wow everyone's like wow so talented amazing it's like that that's great then it's like you know
hey arbiter
looking to attach I know I know I know I mean it's like
but I kind of do fall hard for people and it's like I like and then it's like
it's the whole but that's another narcissist thing it's like okay so it goes
There's like the love bombing phase where it's like everything is good. It's like the honeymoon phase in a way
But it's like that but it's like with a maybe with a friend, right?
And it's like I mean the honeymoon bit we're just like, oh
We just love each other we're so for this close, right?
And it's so then it goes to that and then it goes to like the
Devaluing right right where it's like oh that you kind of be put off your pestle
You're like, you know all of a sudden like they don't care about you anymore. You're like and then then it goes
To discard, you know, you I say basically you love bomb you idealize you do you value and you discard
And then you Hoover and that starts the cycle right back up again because then you start to love bombing again
I say oh, it's back. It's back. It's back
Oh, it is like the golden period of our life. It's like this is okay
We were in this period and it lasts for like such a little time
I think this little happy period like that. It's like everything's perfect
Then it's like we always and then when we get a glimpse of we want it back
And so it's so irresistible, we keep going back to these people because it becomes like an addiction, it becomes like an obsession almost because we want that time we were truly happy, but it was not real and it's like we have to learn it's not real, then it's a whole reality kind of crashes down, it has better.
Alex is in jail
Alex the McQueen is in jail or Alex McQueen or Alex
Yeah, Alex my mayor. I really like Alex mayor by the way. I think she's like a really cool awesome person that is like
Really an example of a survivor and I don't know why she gets a lot of shit from people like judgment about her past or anything
I'd say like, you know
Who are you? Who's anybody to judge her? Okay? Like really or judge me or just like no one should be judging us
And especially us that are putting ourselves out here
Say I don't feel in the mood to talk to you right now. And so I'm not going to you
I'm just gonna chat with my chat, you know
You're seeing I'm not gonna like I don't feel like just dealing with your bullshit right now
You're trying to throw me off and I'll do all those other stuff
You don't do anything except to come up here and talk a bunch of shit to me
And I don't like how your friend came up and like it starts talking about like, you know
the
N-I-N-E-E-L-E-B-E-N stuff.
Like, why was that?
Oh, we went on another, what are you talking about?
You're talking about terrorism on my show?
Are you fucking crazy?
Like, why would you like have him come,
it wasn't a plan to have him come in and say that stupid shit.
It's not just like, he's just dumb talking out of his ass.
It's he's saying like really horrible, like,
terroristic shit.
Like, why would you let that person like,
I'm not responsible for what other people say he comes with you your package deal. Okay, your package deal. You're like Abbott on Costello
Now you if you if you drop off the panel he'll drop off the panel
He's only there because of you trying to impress you. Okay, so okay
Have some control of your friends because he's a very impressionable person obviously
Thing doesn't he had no he has his friends do it
If any of you didn't do it, I'm not responsible.
You just had them come in and say it.
Just like you said on my show that you're
at I'm Alive Yourself on my show, Sig.
Is that appropriate?
Sig.
What, are those things appropriate?
Are those things I should like,
yes, you said that on my show.
They're not appropriate, right?
You're not supposed to say those kind of things.
None of that has occurred, I have it on tape, Sig.
Okay?
You're saying that.
Like why are you trying to like fuck with my show?
So it's like no, I don't feel like having you on and you're like I'm always like
Oh, it might be different or it's like I even like thought you're you know, you weren't the most unattractive person
I've ever seen in my life, but it's like I was like, oh, he's a nice, you know, this guy is interesting or whatever
I would always defend you people say don't have him on don't have him on even your friends would say
Oh, he's the guy don't have him on and then I would and then
And defend you and then you always attack me is like I don't I've ever I don't ever attack you
I mean you do look like a
Fats an old Samo Samoan woman like in her fifties you do. I'm sorry
You do look like the Maori
Statues, you know the stone heads. That's what you just look like that
I'm not I'm just me. I'm not like making fun of you. You actually do look like that
But I don't I don't have them safe so don't worry
You should do I said I look like Abraham Lincoln Jeffrey Dahmer
You know during Goblin was the most unappealing like
You know things I had accused them all the time
No, I'm not letting him up you let him up. How about you do your show Ziggy? Oh, that's right. You don't have a show
Really you guys, I'm I say is that on this show
So much
Okay guys if somebody wants to go on they can sponsor him send $10 and
My cash app is right here, and I will have to go on
I can't guarantee if he starts talking about nonsense like
NIN e l e b n. I can't have them on anymore. I'll just have to like pick them off
But I'll have one if you do donate $10 cash up
And we'll see if anybody really wants them on
Okay, I'll make a banner oh
He's not he's not he's okay now
He didn't like the idea of me actually like you know making a dollar and so he just left and so I'm not gonna have a vector
But if you want to sponsor them, then I'll know I'll save it for next time ten dollars for ten minutes
That sounds good as long as look at this. Oh
in bad faith. Okay, Sig, well, it's not up to you,
it's up to me, it's my show.
And so, you don't need to tell my audience what to do.
See, they're not going to you.
Because, well, he knew they're not going,
see, that's why he went down, though.
He doesn't like the idea.
See, that's why real ones will not care
because they'll want you to have a little extra money.
They'll want you to make sure they'll be like,
That oh, I like that, you know that the person's taking care of and making some money. It's my friend. They're not like oh my god
They're making a you know, that's you said look at people react to your success that will show you who your real friends are
Because those are people that are not only happy for success, but they're helping make you successful
And there's people that are just trying to take away from you and vampire eyes you take away every good thing from you
Take away anybody that even likes you and turn everyone against you and make you a joke and everything that they want
Some people want to do that to you, right?
Say the people that will stick with you are the ones that are like not influenced by that kind of shit
Like people like you guys like an amen. I can see who some of the real ones are. Yeah, I love you, too
Jesus
And I love you Ziggy. I love you ghost, but see go fuck yourself
right
Yeah
No $10 for one minute. That's what it should have been right I can have anything on my in bad faith
What is bad faith? He has bad faith. What does he talk about faith?
What God does he believe in he worships the devil? Okay? I mean geez
Bad faith right
Guys, have I done anything in bad faith?
I've been honest about everything.
I've, thanks for everything.
I don't, if I'm donated to it doesn't mean you own me.
It doesn't mean I'm your bitch.
Like art, like, thank you, Arbiter.
Okay, so there you go.
Thank you, Ghost.
So Ghost, so Ghost said 30 seconds, Sig.
I'll give you 30 seconds.
You know, I'll try now to kick you off before then. You just can't say stuff against COS, but you can come up for
For 30 seconds ghost donated for you. So there you go
Thank you ghost. So you say look
There are there is somebody that is like, you know
But thank you Arbiter. She'll thank you. I appreciate that
Hey Vicky
Yeah, so say you get 30 seconds, but I guess we're gone
You just didn't like the idea of
But he but also he knew that I I could do it. I could you know, I could have got
Yeah
That's that I
Somebody might have and he just didn't like that idea so he couldn't stand that idea that that's he would have had a narcissistic injury like he's
Oh God
So he had to go right I just read my stream. I don't think he can you take off symphony, please?
Symphony number nine you can just hide them
You think well, okay, we'll hold on a second Vicki, huh? So symphony explain yourself. I destroyed my stream with timeouts
What do you like? What do you mean?
Like by having to end the show because they have porn bombs
What are you talking about what they tell me what do you mean by timeouts?
Hold on. Well, if every second that he can't respond, he gets that many more seconds to be on the panel. It's nice for two months, but for no longer.
What are you talking about? Are you speaking English or something? What are you saying?
I destroy my stream with timeouts. It's nice for two months, but for no longer. Am I crazy guys, or does that make no sense?
Oh my god.
Yeah, it's like I mean it's like I don't think maybe you're not trying to be like you don't need to criticize
You just don't have to watch it's like
The hell
Wow
Okay, I'll give you guys it's a little house tour because it's like people like to say I'm like so dirty and well
I sit up too fast. I sit up too fast
I'll be fine. Hold on. Hold on. Okay. I give it respect
Here's my house. Okay, so I have a staircase
So there's my stairs so I good I I'm on above the garage. Okay, so
This is like I know this is messy, I'm sorry
My bedroom is like really messy to you, but
I need to put my laundry like away. I'm the closet full of stuff like really cool stuff
If you look when I'm sure people will pause this and stuff like that look for
Anything I have another room. I'm still cleaning back here. This is a computer room
That's my place and then there use the cats
Are you good? Hi kitty cats. Hi, what are you guys doing?
Hi tricks you good
Hi, good morning. Hi, my little buddy
My buddy
Confederate shirt
Is it I don't know I have I have one with like even more it has like a little bit a bit of leather like down
It's what it was one of my dad's shirts. I wear sometimes
You missed your tricks
You're purring you're purring
You know, oh, how are you Lola? You there Lola? Hi
If over to
Hi, hi, Lola
Six here, okay, you get 30 seconds thing. Hello
But he might like do something else you gave me just here. Let's give him like a woman. Arbiter. You just say stop, okay?
Yeah, Arbiter did donate for like 30 seconds thing, so go ahead
that's Lola. This is the tricks. Yeah, they're oversleeping, but now there's like a big loud left.
All right. So basically, what I do want to say here is in regards to the TOS question,
I think you're moving towards a more stricter direction, but especially in your early streams
It was very you're very loose with TOS very flexible
And and honestly, I haven't said anything or done anything. That's any worse than anybody else that you continue to let on
Say you know I never said I never said that you're gonna drink yourself to DATH on stream
That's what you said. Yes. You did. You said exactly that you were gonna drink yourself to death on stream. That's what you said
Okay, and you have again you have guests you have other guests even if I did say that which I didn't you have
Even if I even if you did say
People that say worse and break the rules worse
You look psyche if you want to say this guy's signal. I don't like this guy and that's it
That's what you said. I
Give you say
Service to you. I don't hear you. I don't hear you. I don't hear you. I don't hear you. I said you can say that
You're breaking the rules
Everybody else that joins your stream questions things
The rules on your stream are very flexible. I understand you're trying to be a little bit more rigid with them.
If everything else is doing it right, it's not fair.
No, it is fair. It is fair because I know it's not. Yes, it is.
Although I want to say I appreciate Arbiter.
For the money and I have no problem with anybody else making money, but you want to be rude to me
You want to be saying things about my appearance and that and then the other and then saying oh, but you can pay money to join
That I that I don't like that's not nice
Problem with that you are shit you were saying about narcissistic abuse
What is that the 12 rules of power or whatever the fuck shit?
That stuff's insane. There's four rules of power or whatever the the Machiavellian that Machiavellian book
Everything that's bizarre dude. No, what do you mean what to look out for you're saying that?
What are you doing narcissistic something?
Like dude, I don't even care, but somebody else
Affect me. I don't care about that. Yes, you were
Well, it's so weird dude, that's so weird just because that's what you are doesn't mean that everybody else is like that
You're projecting you read the 48 laws of power and then you just say projecting
Okay, that's 30 seconds. That was 30 seconds. Hey, I can't take any more arbiter. That was 30 more than 30 seconds
I can't take it. Okay
Yeah
So anyway
He is a narcissist
I mean guys, I'm not just like trying to like call it sometimes when people call people are narcissists
It's they're trying to hide their narcissists. I admit I have narcissistic tendencies, but they're very minimal and they're not malignant
They're like
It's just any basic person in Los Angeles, you know, has to, like, understand, you know,
or have a little self-esteem, you know, so you can call it self-esteem, you can call
it narcissism, you know, because people call everybody narcissists now, right?
I'm saying there's a more extreme version, there's malignant, I mean, it's a lot of different
things.
No, Ziggy. He just a operator paid for 30 seconds. He said 30 seconds
I gave sick like three minutes and then I had enough of him just like
Calling me names the shit. I can have you see so don't tell me what was right. I was not right. I get to decide the rules
I'm gonna play my song again. You have to listen to the words. Okay. This is the rule
They're simple, but y'all can't seem to follow them
So here's a little song to make it real clear
No hate speech, don't test that line
Don't care if it's soft day to hard our time
You say it, you gone, don't play confused
This ain't that show, we don't make those moves
No slander, yeah I said what I said
You toss more fake dirt than a Reddit thread
WWE got nothing on this chat, false accusations
Man, cut that crap
Behave yourself
To the vibe and don't do dumb things
Why's your avatar somebody's face real names real pics this ain't your place posting addresses like it's Halloween
You better send pizza with that scheme. No nudity. We beg and plead Aldi
No one wants your balls on screen flirty diamond stop the solo act those melted kisses ain't bringing sexy back
to the vibe and don't do dumb things this ain't your bathroom concert tour this ain't your only
fans preview this is psyche awakens a sacred space where trolls come to die and souls come to shine
i don't come to your house and poop on the table so don't come to mine and drop a deuce on my
panel respect the host respect the guest or get digitally dragged publicly blessed amen
Don't behave yourself, it ain't that hard
Nah, don't be the chaos in my terrode yard
No slurs, no lies, no nu-
Thinkin' time begins
I mean
You know be more clear. I am a fucking song with the rules in it now. I mean, it's like there's no excuse
Traditional song with the rules. I had to make it so everyone could understand them
Yeah
There we go, I mean, it sounds fine coming undone. Yeah, I like that one. That's good
And but there's also a song called narcissistic cannibal
Yeah, so beautiful
Yeah, it's a good one
Anyway, let me just do a little stage and then I'll let everyone go
We'll get we'll get clear up this energy
Just negative energy. Okay
Audrey I'll read a song too
See you, guys.
Form 93.
Psalm 93 the Lord reigns he is robed in majesty the Lord is robed in majesty and armed with strength
Indeed the world's an established firm and secure your throne was established long ago. You are from all eternity
The seas have lifted up Lord the seas have lifted up their voice the seas have lifted up their pounding waves
Mightier than the thunder of the great waters mightier than the breakers of the sea
Lord on high is mighty your statutes Lord stand firm holiness adorns your house for endless days
Not bad
Anyone have a Psalm they want to throw out? 33. Herbie? Hold on.
Psalm 33.
Seeing joyfully to the Lord, you righteous, it is fitting for the upright to praise and
praise the Lord with his harp. Make music for him on a 10 string liar.
Sing to him a new song, play skillfully, and shout for joy.
For the word of the Lord is right and true, he is faithful in all he does,
the Lord loves righteousness and justice, the earth is full of his unfailing love.
By the word of the Lord the heavens were made, their starry host by the breath of his mouth.
He gathers the waters of the sea into jars.
He puts the deep into storehouses.
Let all the earth fear the Lord.
Let all the people of the world revere Him.
For He spoke, and it came to be.
He commanded, and it stood firm.
The Lord foils the plans of the nations, he thwarts the purposes of the peoples, but
the plans of the Lord stand firm forever, the purposes of his heart through all generations.
Blessed is the nation whose God is the Lord, the people he chose for his inheritance.
From heaven the Lord looks down, and sees all mankind.
From his dwelling place he watches, all who live on earth.
He who forms the hearts of all, who considers everything they do.
No king is saved by the size of his army.
No warrior escapes by his great strength.
A horse is a vain hope for deliverance.
Despite all its great strength, it cannot save, but the eyes of the Lord are on those
who fear him, on those whose hope is in his unfailing love, to deliver them from death
and keep them alive and famine.
We wait in hope for the Lord. He is our hope and our shield in him our hearts rejoice
We trust in his holy name may your unfailing love you with us Lord even as we put our hope in you
I like that one
About Psalm
for the director of music, according to Gitteth of Assoff.
Sing for joy to God our strength, shout aloud to the God of Jacob, begin the music, strike
the timbrel, play the melodious harp and lyre, sound the ram's horn at the new moon, and
when the moon is full on the day of our festival, this is the decree for Israel, in ordinance
of the God of Jacob, when God went out against Egypt, he established it as a statue for Joseph.
I heard an unknown voice say, I removed the burden from their shoulders.
Their hands were set free from the basket.
In your distress, you called out and I rescued you.
I answered you out of a thundercloud.
I tested you at the waters of Marybaw.
Hear me, my people, and I will warn you, if you would only listen to me, Israel, you shall have no foreign gods among you, you shall not worship any God other than me.
I am the Lord your God who brought you up out of Egypt. Open wide your mouth, and I will fill it.
But my people would not listen to me, Israel would not submit to me, so I gave them over to their stubborn hearts to follow their own devices.
If my people would only listen to me, if Israel would only follow my ways,
how quickly I would subdue their enemies and turn my hand against their foes.
Those who hate the Lord would cringe before him, and their punishment would last forever,
which you would be fed with the finance of wheat, with honey from the rock I would satisfy you."
Gospel of Judas, I'll read it. Let's read that. It's short.
It's one of those, you know mysterious Gospels that just pops up hundreds of years later. You live, but yeah, go ahead and believe it
Gospels you just let me see
Okay, here it goes guys
The following translation has been committed to the public domain and maybe freely copied and used, changed or unchanged for any purpose.
It is based on the Coptic text of Codex Tacos 3.
So there's something called Codex Tacos.
Okay, so first of all, it's going to show you this is probably bullshit.
Okay, let's continue for information about the surviving manuscript of the gospel of Jew to see the manuscript information page.
Okay.
Introduction. It starts with page 33 and the Gospel of Judas. That's where it starts.
So it says, this is a secret message of judgments. Jesus spoke with Judas Iscariot over a period of eight days, three days before he celebrated Passover.
When he appeared on earth, he did signs and great wonders for the salvation of humanity.
Some walked in the way of righteousness, but others walked in their transgression.
So 12 disciples were called.
He started to tell them about the mysteries behind the world and what would happen at
the end.
Often, he didn't reveal himself to his disciples, but you'd find him in their midst as a child.
Oh, Jesus criticizes the disciples.
One day, he was with his disciples in Judea.
He found them sitting together, practicing their piety.
When he came up to his disciples,
together sitting, praying over the bread, he laughed.
The disciples said to him,
Master, why are you laughing at our prayer?
What have we done?
That this is what's right.
He answered and said to them, I'm not laughing at you.
You're not doing this because you want to, but because you, through you, through this your God will be pleased.
They said, Master, you are the son of our God. Jesus said to them, how do you know me?
Truly, I say to you, no generation of the people among you will know me.
Well, wasn't he like there?
When his disciples heard this they started to get angry and furious and started to curse them in her heart
But when Jesus noticed their ignorance he said to them
Why are you letting your anger trouble you? Has your God within you and his stars become angry with your souls?
Is any of you strong enough among humans to bring out this perfect humanity?
Stand up and face me. All of them said we're strong enough but their spirits weren't brave enough to stand before him
except Judas Iscariot
He was able to stand before him, but he couldn't look him in the eyes when he looked away.
Judas said to him, I know who you are and where you've come from.
You've come from the immortal realm of Barbello.
And I'm not worried that you utter the name of the one who sent you, Sophia.
Then Jesus, knowing that he was thinking about what's exalted, said to him,
come away from the others and I'll tell you the mysteries of the kingdom.
Not so that you'll go there, but you'll grieve much because someone else will replace you to complete the 12 elements before they're God.
Judas said to him,
when will you tell me these things and when will the great day of light dawn for the generation?
But when he said these things, Jesus left him.
The next morning he appeared to his disciples, and they said to him, Master, where did you
go and what did you do before you left us?
Or when you left us, Jesus said to them, I went to another great and holy generation.
His disciples said to him, Lord, what great generation is better than holy than us?
That's not in these realms. Now, when Jesus heard this, he laughed. He said to them,
Why are you wondering in your hearts about the strong and holy generation?
Truly, I say to you that no one born of this realm will see that generation.
No army of angels from the stars will rule over it,
and no person of mortal birth will be able to join it, because that generation doesn't come from
And then it's the word is scribbled out that has become blank the generations of the people among them is from the generation of the great
People blank the powerful authorities who blank not
Nor their powers blank those by which you rule something the principalities powerful authorities
Okay, when his disciples heard these things they were each troubled in their spirit
They couldn't say a thing the disciples vision. Oh my god. It's long. It's long. Oh, I'm sorry. It's a long guys
You guys want to hear anymore? I'll go straight to the betrayal.
It says, Jesus said,
Truly I say to you, this baptism which Saviour received in my name will destroy the whole generation of the earth the atom.
Tomorrow they'll torture the one who bears me.
Truly I say to you, no hand of a mortal human will fall upon me.
Truly I say to you, Judas, those who offer sacrifices to Saklas, who's like a lion deity, everything that's evil.
But, you'll do more than all of them, because you'll sacrifice the human who bears me.
Your horn has already been raised, your anger has been kindled, your star has ascended,
and your heart has strayed.
Truly, I say to you, your last, blank, and the thrones of the realm have been defeated,
the kings have grown weak, the angelic generations have grieved, and the evil they sowed is destroyed,
and the rulers wiped out, and in the fruit of the great generation of Adam will be exalted.
earth and the angels that generation from the realm exists. Look, you've been told everything.
Lift up your eyes and see with the cloud, with the light and the stars around it and the star
that leads the way is your star. Then Judas looked up and saw the luminous cloud and he entered it.
Those standing on the ground heard a voice from the cloud saying, the great generation.
and Judas didn't see Jesus anymore.
Immediately there was a disturbance among the Jews.
More than ever, their high priest rumbled
because he'd gone into the guest room to pray.
The subscribers were there watching closely
during his prayer because they were afraid of the people
since they all regarded him as the prophet.
And they approached Judas and said to him,
what are you doing here?
Aren't you Jesus' disciple?
Then he answered them as they wished
and Judas received some money and handed him over to them.
I don't like it.
Hmm
Not the not stick stuff is all written recently
Really it was none of it was like really found they didn't have
Really books back then that they would write this stuff down. They just came up with a printing press like you know very recently
1500s so most of this up is like 500 years old. I'm sorry to break it to you guys
The world is fake